justforfunytvideos.com 2011-09-30

# Privacy Policy | DiGiTs Show

Your privacy is very important to Driver Digital Holdings LLC. (sometimes referred to as "we,"  "us," "our," or "DRIVER"), and we are committed to respecting your privacy on this site. In order to provide our services (the "Services"), we may require information regarding you (sometimes referred to as the "User"). We will maintain the confidentiality of information provided in accordance with our Privacy Policy.  We may change this policy from time to time, and if we do we will provide notice on this Web Site regarding any changes to this policy.

## 1. Information That Is Personally Identifiable

Except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, our current policy is to refrain from selling, leasing, or otherwise transferring your personally identifiable information. 

The information we collect will be maintained in a file that we may need to review in a variety of circumstances, such as enforcing our Terms of Use for Users, analyzing and understanding our customers and their needs, and for the administration and provision of our goods and services. 

As a User of the Service, you consent to the aforementioned uses of such information and the provision of information to service providers that facilitate the Service, all in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

## 2. Aggregate Information

Subject to the other terms of our Privacy Policy, we may aggregate (i.e., assemble on a basis that does not enable one to personally identify you) the data that is acquired under or in connection with this site and/or related to ordering our products and services, including, without limitation, data about the products and services requested and purchased by our Users. Aggregated data may be used by us to improve our Service and for marketing purposes, and may be shared with and used by advertisers and other third parties. We may also use such data to determine what types of policies are best suited for our customers and what types of policies our customers request. If we provide aggregated data to third parties, particular personal information (including birth date, name, title, income, home address, dependent information and any other identifying information) will not be individually identifiable in the aggregated data.

Notwithstanding anything in this privacy policy to the contrary, DRIVER has contracted with third parties to provide tracking and analysis of information and data collected from visitors to our website. DRIVER reserves the right to provide that information and data to such third parties for those purposes. Such information and data is provided on a basis that does not enable a third party to identify you.  Your use of the Service constitutes your consent to the use of such data on an aggregated basis.

## 3. Policy on Children’s Use of the Web Site

This Web Site is, generally, directed at persons over the age of 18 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from or about children under the age of 18. If we, at any time, learn that information relating to a child under the age of 18 that we have obtained is other than as set forth above, we shall immediately purge such information from our records.

## 4. Cookies

Like most other Web Sites, DRIVER’s servers may automatically track certain information about activity on our Web Site. This information allows us to keep our Web Site running efficiently. This information may include: the browser being used (such as Netscape, Internet Explorer, etc.); your operating system (such as Macintosh, Windows, etc.); your IP address; and the referring URL and all company URL’s you visit. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web Site, but your IP address is not connected to information that is personally identifiable.

In addition, DRIVER may use "cookies" on certain pages of our Web Site to automatically collect information from a User to our Web Site and transfer this information to the User’s hard drive. Cookies help us recognize repeat visitors, allowing communication of a personalized welcome message and tailoring of content to match particular interests.  

We also may use outside advertising companies to display advertisements on our Web Site. These advertisements may also contain cookies. Some customer data may be shared with the advertising affiliates on an aggregated basis in accordance with the other terms of this Privacy Policy. Because cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our Web Site, you are always free to set your browser to decline cookies and you can delete them from your computer. If you decline "cookies" or delete them from your computer, you will still be able to access our Web Site, but you may find that some areas do not work as smoothly as when cookies are enabled on your system.

## 5. Other Use

It is possible that DRIVER, its business and/or assets, its present or future subsidiaries, joint ventures or any combination of such, could merge with or be acquired in one or more types of transactions by another business entity or entities. Should such transaction(s) occur, DRIVER has your permission to share some or all of your information in order to, among other things, facilitate continuation of one or more services similar to all or a portion of the Service. Notice of such an event (to the extent that it takes place) will be posted on this Web Site and we will require that the new combined entity adhere to the practices disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

## 6. Disclosure for Legal Purposes

Given the government's current interest in Internet regulation, you hereby authorize us to disclose information pursuant to judicial and administrative proceedings, and in connection with law enforcement activities and as otherwise may be permitted by law, to law enforcement or government agencies if we believe the disclosure is necessary or appropriate. You also authorize us to disclose information if we believe the disclosure is necessary or appropriate in the event of an investigation of improper or illegal conduct in connection with our Web Site, such as fraud, misrepresentation, intellectual property infringement, or other activity that may put us at risk for liability. We will, whenever we believe reasonably possible, use our reasonable efforts to inform a User whose information may be so revealed.

## 7. Other Parties and Your Information

This policy only relates to our collection and use of your information, except as otherwise provided. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of promotional affiliates or other third parties to which we may provide links. DRIVER does not have control over the privacy policies applied by any other party that you may disclose information to when linking to from our Web Site. If you would like information on any other party's privacy policy, you should contact that party directly, and we encourage you to do so.

## 8.Security

DRIVER employs standard industry measures to protect and ensure the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, including the use of firewalls and SSL encryption. Despite these efforts, we cannot guarantee the security of your information given the current state of the Internet. We also do not undertake to maintain information about you for a duration greater than as provided by law, rule or regulation.   

DRIVER engages in other security measures, as follows:

Physical security of the systems against theft and damage;

Software integrity to ensure that only authorized personnel can implement or modify software;

Disaster recovery planning processes and systems;

Data integrity to check the validity of certain data; and

Data security administration procedures to ensure proper monitoring and auditing. 

We believe we employ security measures that adequately address the security needs of DRIVER visitors.

You may write a request through the US mail system to us at 

Driver Digital Holdings LLC    
Attention: Legal Department  
9454 Wilshire Blvd, Suite 850  
Beverly Hills, CA 90212

Tel: 310-275-0562  
Fax: 310-275-0563  
Email: [fassistant@rfgllaw.com](mailto:%C2%A0efassistant@rfgllaw.com)
